- id: ckw-l11-2741
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2744
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - プレゼント
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2793
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コピー
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2804
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カレー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2806
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ゴルフ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2831
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ケア
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2837
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レストラン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2846
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テル
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2846
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - トラブル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2853
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カット
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2861
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ライブ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2864
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ショー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2872
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - キログラム
  hint: "noun/counter"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2878
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - サッカー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l11-2884
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - クリスマス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
